Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers 1966-2000 MSS 156
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Andrea Callard Artist Files
  - Subseries H: Art Education
    - Whistle Stop Daycare. Color copy of photograph., ca. 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Bronx Museum of Arts. Eight color slides, event program and letter of recommendation., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Teaching-Malone file. includes letters from students, 53 color slides [grouped by AC], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Teaching-Malone file. 29 color slides and a Christmas card. [grouped by AC], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Hecksher. Letter and 12 color slides., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Black River file. Includes student letters, sketchbook, press clippings. [grouped by AC], 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - "Black River Residency" file. Press and 138 color slides., 1984 [grouped by AC] (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts. File contans press, contact information, school mailings, notes, planning letters etc., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts Student Letters, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Student "Love Letters" from Rockland students. Part 1, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - "Love Letters" from Rockland students. Part 2, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Rockland Arts-in-Education Showcase. April 1, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - New York State Summer School of the Arts. FIle includes black and white photographs, contact sheets and negatives as well as notes, contact information and promotional materials., 1990 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Paper-making workshop for Studio in a School., 1990 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Andrea Callard with students., undated (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Lower East Side Printshop. Andrea Callard screenprinting materals demonstration., undated (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Notes and printed materials relating to pedagogical techniques., undated (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Subseries I: Miscellaneous materials
    - Notebook. includes sketches, lists, dreams and other writing., undated (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Notebook. Includes drawings, sketches and text., undated (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Notebook. Includes text and ink printing., undated (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Notebook. Includes text, inserts and sketches., undated (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Notebook. Includes text and sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Notebook. Includes text, sketches, letters., undated (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Notebook. Planning notes, some references to Colab. Includes inserts., undated (Box 4, Folder 396)
    - Notebook. Includes drawings and stampings., undated (Box 4, Folder 397)
    - Notebook. Includes ideas, lists, drawings and planning sketches., undated (Box 4, Folder 398)
    - Notebook. Includes lists of expenses, pencil drawings and some text., undated (Box 4, Folder 399)
    - Notebook. Includes sketches, watercolor and writing., undated (Box 4, Folder 400)
    - Notebook. Notes,lists and planning sketches., undated (Box 5, Folder 401)
    - Miscellaneous Press, undated (Box 5, Folder 402)
    - Film Idea fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 406)
    - Video planning. informal "Video Proposal" outline., undated (Box 5, Folder 407)
    - "Irrevocable Time", undated (Box 5, Folder 408)
    - Life Spacing: An exercise. Notes and planning., undated (Box 5, Folder 409)
    - Concentration Booth. Installation collaboration between Andrea Callard, Reese Williams and Winifred Carroll., undated (Box 5, Folder 410)
    - "Fuck You Fashions", undated (Box 5, Folder 411)
    - Household bug paintings., undated (Box 5, Folder 412)
    - Doodlings and Balderdash notes. grouped by AC., undated (Box 5, Folder 413)
    - Crayon and paint on white paper., undated (Box 5, Folder 415)
    - Color printed pages. Includes "Musical Yellow Taxi", undated (Box 5, Folder 416)
    - "Vidi View" diagram, undated (Box 5, Folder 417)
    - Notecards. writing, pencil drawing, watercolor, collage, pen drawing. Grouped by AC., undated (Box 5, Folder 418)
    - Filebox containing notecards. Content on cards includes writing, lists, drawings, collage and photographs. Miscellaneous dates. Grouped by AC., undated (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Drawings, grouped in envelope and labeled "Drawings", undated (Box 5, Folder 421)
    - Rubbings, undated (Box 5, Folder 422)
    - Broken toe print, undated (Box 5, Folder 423)
    - "A Bridge from Memory, A Channel for Love", undated (Box 5, Folder 424)
    - Label: "This green ladder functions...", undated (Box 5, Folder 425)
    - Stickers of alphabet and numbers, undated (Box 5, Folder 426)
    - "Double Lunar Dogs" written and directed by Joan Jonas. Sets and control panel by Andrea Callard., undated (Box 5, Folder 427)
    - Andrea Callard drawing fo Spanner Paper Suit, undated (Box 5, Folder 428)
    - Miscellaneous prints on paper., undated (Box 5, Folder 429)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of a woman posing., undated (Box 5, Folder 431)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of building exteriors and a mason jar., undated (Box 5, Folder 432)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. "Statue" Reese Williams and Corine Stachner, undated (Box 5, Folder 433)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Ed Chaplin "Confusciors", undated (Box 5, Folder 434)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of rural and industrial buildings, trees., undated (Box 5, Folder 435)
    - Black and white negatives and contact frame. Image of man at desk, shell and Clark buildings., undated (Box 5, Folder 436)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of building demolition., undated (Box 5, Folder 437)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Andrea Callard and Fred Krughoff., undated (Box 5, Folder 438)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Chicago and Andrea Callard's Father's second family., undated (Box 5, Folder 439)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Andrea Callard and Gary Brown., undated (Box 5, Folder 440)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Andrea Callard, Gary Brown and Berta Callard, undated (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trees, Andrea Callard and friends, newspapers., undated (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Black and white cpntact sheet. Images of Andrea Callard's loft at 40 Lispenard and Fred Krughoff's loft on Water St. Undated but post 1976. (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Joshua Tree and 29 Palms with Baylor Trapnell., undated (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Images of kids and parking meters., undated (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of kids, pets, newspaper., undated (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Color photograph printed on white paper. Image of messy desk., undated (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of roots and kids., undated (Box 5, Folder 448)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Andrea Callard and young boy, probably her son., undated (Box 5, Folder 449)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of kids, trees, chain and brickwork., undated (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Black and white negatives of New York., undated (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Black and white photographs, miscellaneous images., undated (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Black and white negative. Images of trees., undated (Box 5, Folder 454)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of hands and feet., undated (Box 5, Folder 455)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Bangles and a woman standing., undated (Box 5, Folder 456)
    - Miscellaneous color slides, unlabeled, undated (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of building exteriors and birds on a streetlight., undated (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - Black and white copntact sheet and negatives. Images of car on George Washington Bridge and in parking lot., undated (Box 5, Folder 459)
    - Black and white negatives and contact seets. Images of trees and buildings in winter., undated (Box 5, Folder 460)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of construction site., undated (Box 5, Folder 461)
    - Miscellaneous black and white photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 463)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of an unknown woman talking., undated (Box 5, Folder 464)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of outside., undated (Box 5, Folder 465)
    - Black and white black and white negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 466)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of satelite dish., undated (Box 5, Folder 467)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of a party., undated (Box 5, Folder 468)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of water, trees, trash., undated (Box 5, Folder 469)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Halloween, supper, toys., undated (Box 5, Folder 470)
    - Misc. color negatives of horses and satelite dish, undated (Box 5, Folder 471)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trees and a house., undated (Box 5, Folder 472)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet.Images of unknown woman at her computer., undated (Box 5, Folder 473)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of garbage, park with child, playground., undated (Box 5, Folder 474)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trashcans., undated (Box 5, Folder 475)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of building ornaments, undated (Box 5, Folder 476)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of unknown man speaking., undated (Box 5, Folder 477)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of outdoors., undated (Box 5, Folder 478)
    - Color photo collage of roadtrip., undated (Box 5, Folder 479)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets "Bride on the Bridge" photo collboration between Corine Schactner and Andrea Callard, undated (Box 5, Folder 480)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Bernice Rubin, Cara Perlman and Richard Friedman., undated (Box 5, Folder 482)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of trashcans, bagpipes and kids., undated (Box 5, Folder 483)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trashcans and kids., undated (Box 5, Folder 485)
    - Miscellaneous color negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 486)
    - Color negatives and snapshots. Documenting color and texture as, undated (Box 5, Folder 487)
    - Color negatives. unlabeled. undated (Box 5, Folder 488)
    - Black and white negatives. unlabeled. undated. (Box 5, Folder 489)
    - Color photographs printed on paper., undated (Box 5, Folder 490)
    - Black and white negatives. Laurie Binder in Vermont., undated (Box 5, Folder 491)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Reese Williams with Brick and Megan at 40 Lispenard. Undated, post 1976 (Box 5, Folder 492)
    - Black and white contact sheets. Images of Andrea Callard, driving, snow and monuments., undated (Box 5, Folder 493)
    - Black and white negatives. Documentation of drawings., undated (Box 5, Folder 494)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of trees on Lispenard., undated (Box 5, Folder 495)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of sculpture with branches, dog and woman., undated (Box 5, Folder 496)
    - Black and white photograph of Dog [Brick?] outside black tent, indoors., undated (Box 5, Folder 497)
    - Drawing, photograph and instructions grouped together in folder., undated (Box 5, Folder 498)
- Series III: Administrative
  Series III: Administrative is divided into seven subseries. Subseries A includes grant proposals, calls for proposals, resumes and other materials relating to obtaining professional appointments and work. Subseries B includes paperwork regarding artworks loaned by Andrea Callard. Subseries C includes financial information such as receipts and taxes. Subseries D contains information regarding Andrea Callard's participation in organizations, for example her work with LINE. Subseries E contains employment information for student interns who worked with Andrea Callard. Subseries F includes paperwork relating to Andrea Callard's day to day work as an artist such as notes, lists and research copies. Finally, Subseries G includes artist photographs. Subseries arranged chronologically where possible, alphabetically in other instances.
  - Subseries A: Grants
    - Application to Cummington Community of the Arts, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 499)
    - Summary of Career Activity, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 500)
    - Resume, ca. 1979 (Box 5, Folder 501)
    - Public Art at the World Trade Center book, Call for submissions., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 502)
    - Notes on documents supplied with grant application, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 503)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts artist in residence program., 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 504)
    - Application materials for unknown art opportunity, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 505)
    - Public Art Fund, Bryant Park AIR residency application, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 506)
    - Art Park residency, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 507)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University file. Invitation to particiape in 1984-1985 Artist Forum. (Box 5, Folder 508)
    - Resume, ca 1985 (Box 5, Folder 510)
    - Cover letter and CV drafts, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 511)
    - Proposal for "Birds and Trowels" at the Anchorage, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 512)
    - Cityarts Workshop, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 513)
    - Art Matters, Inc. application for mural project., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 514)
    - "Neighborhood Climate" Application to New York State Council on the Arts Visual Artists Sponsored Projects., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 515)
    - Burchfield Art Center new works residency., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 516)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts artist in residency planning and oreintation workshop packet. Andrea Callard's Rockland residency., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 517)
    - Letter of inquiry to Rasnova/Laurie Yarotski Art Gallery, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 518)
    - Garden Projects, application and proposal for Harlem Rehabilitation Center, Hopkinson R and L Block Association and Good Neighbor Block Association., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 519)
    - Chicago Books, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 520)
    - Documentation to Municipal Arts Society regarding "The Tenement" installation at Chinatown History Project and DIA., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 521)
    - Anchor Foundation Incorporated application to Cultural Council FOundation., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 523)
    - Proposal for Rutgers Archives Printo Commission by Andrea Callard and Rand Russell., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 524)
    - Studio in a School Association, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 525)
    - Brendan Gill Prize information, undated (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - Subseries B: Artwork loans
    - Insurance form, Custom and Culture part II, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 528)
    - MoMA "Committed to Print" show, Andrea Callard loaned Kiki Smith, Charlie Ahearn and Jane Dickson's "Cause/Effect" from Colab's street posters., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 529)
  - Subseries C: Finances
    - Income Tax audit, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 530)
    - Motion Picture Laboratories Invoice, found in Media Box 4, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 531)
    - Receipt: Standard Adult Wheelchair, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 532)
    - "The Tenement" tax exempt paperwork, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 533)
    - "The Tenement" receipts, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 534)
    - "The Tenement" budget, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 535)
    - "The Tenement" at DIA, receipts, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 536)
    - Miscellaneous receipts, undated (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - Subseries D: Organizational Participation
    - LINE Request For Proposals. LINE was a "service organization of artists that assists other artists with small grants for publication projects.", 1979 (Box 5, Folder 539)
    - Manhattan Decentralization panelist handbook, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 540)
    - Manhattan Decentralization Program recipient list., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 541)
    - Artists Call against US intervention in Central America, undated (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - Subseries E: Interns
    - Ning, Stephan C., 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 543)
    - Rees, Sarah, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - Subseries F: Notes and Research copies
    - Ailanthus research copies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 545)
    - Housing advocacy, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 546)
    - Recycling research copies, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 548)
    - Recycling research, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 549)
    - Miscellaneous notes and lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 550)
    - Newspaper clipping "Wrist Camera Needs No Darkroom", undated (Box 5, Folder 551)
    - page 25-26 of Neil Postman's Amusing Ourselves to Death., undated (Box 5, Folder 552)
    - New Yorker cartoons, undated (Box 5, Folder 553)
    - "The 'Youth Protest' and the 'Age of Creativity'" Pinchas Noy, undated (Box 5, Folder 554)
    - Nature clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - Subseries G: Artist Photographs
    - Fred Krughoff photographs of Andrea Callard. Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Late 1970s, ca. 1978 (Box 6, Folder 556)
    - Callard portraits by Teri Slotkin prior to Malone Residency. Black and white contact sheets, three color slides, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 557)
    - Peter Bellamy portraits of Andrea Callard. Used for her profile in "The Artist Book". Black and white contact sheets., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 558)
    - Unknown photographer, portraits of Andrea Callard. Black and white negatives and contact sheet, undated (Box 6, Folder 559)
    - Fred Krughoof portraits of Andrea Callard. also includes images of Alan Saret. Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Taken post 1976, at Lispenard., undated (Box 6, Folder 560)
- Series IV: Other Artist Files
  Series IV: Other Artist Files includes individual and group artist files arranged alphabetically. The series is divided into three suseries. Subseries A includes Individual artist files arranged alphabetically by last name. Subseries B includes group projects arranged chronologically. Subseries C includes miscellaneous and unknown materials.
  - Subseries A: Individual artist files
    - ABC NO RIO Cardboard Air Band., undated (Box 6, Folder 561)
    - Acconci, Vito, undated (Box 6, Folder 562)
    - Arai, Tomie, undated (Box 6, Folder 565)
    - Becket, Mack, undated (Box 6, Folder 566)
    - Bellamy, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 567)
    - Blane, Marc, undated (Box 6, Folder 568)
    - Brown, Barbara Miller, undated (Box 6, Folder 569)
    - Caldwell, Catherine [Randi], undated (Box 6, Folder 570)
    - Callan, Trissy, undated (Box 6, Folder 581)
    - Cardoso, Maria Fernand, undated (Box 6, Folder 582)
    - Carpi, Cioni, undated (Box 6, Folder 583)
    - Chadha, Gurinder, undated (Box 6, Folder 584)
    - Corber, Mitch, undated (Box 6, Folder 586)
    - Crowe, Susan Spencer, undated (Box 6, Folder 587)
    - Dickson, Jane, undated (Box 6, Folder 588)
    - Ernst, Max, undated (Box 6, Folder 589)
    - Fend, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 590)
    - Geller, Matthew, undated (Box 6, Folder 591)
    - Glier, Mike, undated (Box 6, Folder 592)
    - Haring, Keith, undated (Box 6, Folder 594)
    - Hodgkin, Howard, undated (Box 6, Folder 595)
    - Hurbide, Graciela, undated (Box 6, Folder 598)
    - Jones, Juan, undated (Box 6, Folder 599)
    - Kahane, Lisa, undated (Box 6, Folder 600)
    - Kohlhofer, Christof, undated (Box 6, Folder 601)
    - Korns, Stephen, undated (Box 6, Folder 602)
    - Krughoff, Fred, undated (Box 6, Folder 603)
    - Laub, Steven, undated (Box 6, Folder 604)
    - Lee, Jung Jin, undated (Box 6, Folder 605)
    - Linder, Alf, undated (Box 6, Folder 606)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated (Box 6, Folder 607)
    - Mock, Richard Basil. Access copies of New York Times artworks, undated (Box 6, Folder 608)
    - Naito, Jiro, undated (Box 6, Folder 612)
    - Nathan, Gail, undated (Box 6, Folder 613)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, undated (Box 6, Folder 615)
    - Nichols, Alice W., undated (Box 6, Folder 616)
    - Otterness, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 617)
    - Perlman, Cara, undated (Box 6, Folder 618)
    - Roddy, Mike, undated (Box 6, Folder 619)
    - Rupp, Christy, undated (Box 6, Folder 620)
    - Saaar, Alison, undated (Box 6, Folder 621)
    - Saret, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 622)
    - Seltman, R.L., undated (Box 6, Folder 623)
    - Schaumburger, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 625)
    - Sidburney, Alex, undated (Box 6, Folder 626)
    - Smith, Martin, undated (Box 6, Folder 627)
    - Sussler, Betsy, undated (Box 6, Folder 628)
    - Takenaga, Barbara, undated (Box 6, Folder 629)
    - Trapnell, Baylor, undated (Box 6, Folder 631)
    - Turre, Michele, undated (Box 6, Folder 632)
    - Viner, Frank Lincoln, undated (Box 6, Folder 633)
    - Warren, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 634)
    - Waters, Jonathan, undated (Box 6, Folder 635)
    - Weitzman, Lee, undated (Box 6, Folder 636)
    - Williams, Reese, undated (Box 6, Folder 638)
    - Williamson, Philemona, undated (Box 6, Folder 639)
    - Winters, Robin, undated (Box 6, Folder 640)
    - Wirsum, Karl, undated (Box 6, Folder 641)
    - Youngblood, Daisy, undated (Box 6, Folder 642)
  - Subseries B: Collaborations and Group Shows
    - AICA invitation, undated (Box 6, Folder 643)
    - "Life Mixing" includes Reese Williams, Theresa Cha, Maxine Borenstein, Ed Harker and Brian Mealins, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 645)
    - "Practical Esthetic Services" business card. Includes Fend, Fitzgibbon, Holzer, Nadin, Prince and Winters., undated (Box 6, Folder 646)
    - Miscellaneous collaborations and group shows., undated (Box 6, Folder 648)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous and Unknown Artists
    - Graffitti style drawing, undated (Box 6, Folder 649)
    - Color photographs of Cara Perlman, ca. 1978 (Box 6, Folder 651)
    - Miscellaneous images on white paper, undated (Box 6, Folder 652)
    - Faux advertisements with type and circles, undated (Box 6, Folder 657)
    - Black and white negatives, Fashion Moda, Corona park, undated (Box 6, Folder 659)
    - Black and white negatives, White Columns, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 661)
- Series V: Correspondence
  Series V: Correspondence includes Andrea Callard's personal and administrative correspondence organized alphabetically by sender. The series is divided into four subseries. Subseries A contains correspondence from senders with known first and last names arranged alphabetically by last name. Subseries B includes correspondence from senders with known first names or first initials organized alphbetically. Subseries C contains correspondence from Andrea callard organized alphabetically by addressee. Subseries D includes unlabeld or illegible correspondence.
  - Subseries A: Last name, First name
    - Amdur, Latifa, undated (Box 6, Folder 663)
    - Antenen, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 664)
    - Art In America, undated (Box 6, Folder 665)
    - Artists Space, undated (Box 6, Folder 666)
    - Artlink Artspace, undated (Box 6, Folder 667)
    - Atcher, R.W., undated (Box 6, Folder 668)
    - Becket, Mac, undated (Box 6, Folder 669)
    - Bellamy, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 670)
    - Binder, Laurie, undated (Box 6, Folder 671)
    - Blanchet, Jo, undated (Box 6, Folder 672)
    - Brown, Duncan, undated (Box 6, Folder 673)
    - Brown, Gary, undated (Box 6, Folder 674)
    - Burns, Mark [Tribeca-SoHo Animal Hospital], undated (Box 6, Folder 675)
    - Callard, Mrs. C.G. [Gram], undated (Box 6, Folder 676)
    - Callard, C.G. [Gramp], undated (Box 6, Folder 677)
    - Callard, Roberta [sister], undated (Box 6, Folder 678)
    - Cha, Theresa, undated (Box 6, Folder 679)
    - Chaplin, Ed, undated (Box 6, Folder 680)
    - Cohen, Marjorie, undated (Box 6, Folder 681)
    - Cooper, Ellen, undated (Box 6, Folder 682)
    - Corber, Anne, undated (Box 6, Folder 683)